zalebs.com 2016-04-21

# Zalebs

Privacy policy

Privacy Policy of Zalebs, property of Kagiso Broadcasting (Proprietary) Limited of 1st Floor, Kagiso Tiso House, 100 West Street, Wierda Valley, Sandton 2196.

Effective 1 January 2013

**Privacy Policy Table Of Contents:**

Our Commitment To Privacy

The Information We Collect

When Do We Collect Your Personal Information

What We Do With Your Information

With Whom Is Your Information Shared

Third Party Personal Information

General Use And Records

Our Commitment To Data Security

Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

How You Can Access And Correct Your Information

Commenting And Other Non-Personal Information

Amendments To This Privacy Policy

Governing Law

How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy   **

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

We protect your personal information and only use and disclose your personal information in compliance with applicable law.

BY CLICKING ON THE “I ACCEPT” ICON WHEN YOU SUBMIT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, YOU AGREE, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, TO ACCEPT THE PRIVACY POLICY AND TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS AND CONDITIONS, EXPRESSLY CONSENT AND AGREE TO ALLOW US TO COLLECT, RECEIVE, RECORD, ORGANISE, COLLATE, STORE, UPDATE, MODIFY, RETRIEVE, ALTER, CONSULT, USE, DISSEMINATE, DISCLOSE AND PROCESS PERSONAL INFORMATION AS PROVIDED FOR IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND YOU CONFIRM THAT YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL CONSTITUTE YOUR EXPRESS WRITTEN PERMISSION FOR US TO DO SO.

**The Information We Collect**

This policy applies to all personal information collected or submitted on our website and/or by other electronic means, including by electronic mail and any message sent by mobile phone (including SMS).

We collect the following types of personal information from you:

Name

Address

Email address

Phone number

IP address

After identifying numbers information/addresses

Gender

Age group

Preferences, including brand preferences and general interest

Hobbies and behaviour patterns

Visual images such as vidoes and photographs

**When Do We Collect Your Personal Information**

We collect your personal information when you -

Register and create a profile on our website

Contribute to blogs and forums

Register to receive materials

Enter competitions

View videos

Access or request specific information

Submit information by pther electronic means, for example, by SMS

From facebook.com or other social networking sites, if you log into the website using your Facebook or other social networking sites account.

From time to time, we may require additional personal information specific to a feature or competition. This information will be treated the same as the information described above.

We also use cookies which are stored on your computer, mobile phone or other device in order to enhance your use of the website. For example, we use cookies to determine when you log onto the website, or to know when you are interacting with any other party through our website.

We may also use cookies to identify details such as your IP address, browser type and domain name; and to track your use of our websites, click stream data, preferences and areas of interest and to tailor your view of the website to you and what we understand to be your specific interests.

You may, at any time, remove or block cookies, although this may impact on the way you experience the website.

On the website, we will endeavour to indicate what personal information is mandatory for the purposes of the intended use, and what personal information may be submitted voluntarily. We encourage you to submit voluntary information in order to enhance your use of the website.

**What We Do With Your Information**

We use your personal information for purposes of improving our website, developing and customising products and services better suited to your needs.

If you expressly consent to us using your personal information for marketing purposes, we may also use it to send you relevant marketing, promotional and advertising material, newsletters and other communications offering you products and information about products and services (including by means of direct marketing) offered by us, our affiliates and other third party providers from time to time, which products and services we think may be of interest to you.

Any communication we send you for the purpose of direct marketing will contain contact details to which you may send a request that such communications cease.

We use your information you provide when donating to a charity, placing an order or request, to complete the donation, order or request, and when entering a competition for billing purposes, administration purposes and troubleshooting purposes.

We also use return email addresses and other contact details to answer the email and other communications we receive from you to provide you with the benefits contemplated under this privacy policy.

**With Whom Is Your Information Shared?**

We will not, unless it’s with your consent, share any of your personal information with any third party (save to the extent strictly necessary to give effect to the purposes set out in this privacy policy).

Information you submit when you register on our website will not be used for purposes of direct marketing, sending you information, updates on special inserts and competitions, unless you fill out the relevant registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify any specific individuals.

We also use the information we collect to compile statistical data, and to compile profiles for statistical purposes about website users. We may create and trade with such profiles and statistical data, but we ensure that the information so disclosed cannot be linked to any specific individual.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described in this privacy policy without your consent, save to the extent that we are permitted or required to do so by law.

You agree and confirm that, in the event that we receive any consent or permission or confirmation of consent or permission sent from your email address or mobile phone as submitted on our website, then we shall be entitled to rely on such consent or permission, and it shall be deemed as having been sent by you or on your behalf.

**Third Party Personal Information**

On some pages, you can submit other people’s personal information.

TO THE EXTENT THAT YOU SUBMIT PERSONAL INFORMATION OF ANY OTHER PERSON, YOU HEREBY WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE OBTAINED SUCH PERSON’S CONSENT TO SUBMIT SUCH INFORMATION TO US, ON THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**General Use And Records**

We may also disclose your personal information if and to the extent we are required by law or regulatory authority to do so.

For as long as we consider that your personal information is of use as contemplated in this privacy policy, and for a period of at least one year thereafter, we shall:

Keep a record of your personal information and the specific purpose for which such personal information was collected; and

Keep a record of any third party to whom the personal information was disclosed and of the date on which and the purpose for which it was disclosed.

We shall delete or destroy all personal information which we consider has become obsolete.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain personal information on our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

By clicking on the “I AGREE” icon you warrant that you are over 18 or that you are submitting your personal information with the assistance of a competent person who is over the age of 18.

**How You Can Access and Correct Your Information**

You have access to your profile at all times and may update or correct your personal information on your profile at any time.

You have a right to request us to confirm whether or not we hold personal information about you, and to request that we describe any such information to you, and you have a right to request that the information be corrected or deleted.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections, which may include the use of passwords. You must carefully safeguard any password provided to and/or used by you in relation to such access, and immediately notify us should there be any unauthorised use of such password.

We may put in place facilities that enable you to comment or provide other non-personal information on the website. Once your comments are online, everyone will have access to it. In this regard, you are advised to exercise caution when making comments.

**Amendments To This Privacy Policy**

We may amend this policy from time to time to have regard for changes in the law and in accordance with our requirements. We will post any updates and amendments on our website. It is important that you review this policy regularly so that you are aware of any amendments.

**Governing Law**

This policy is governed by the law of the Republic of South Africa and any legal action instituted in connection with this policy shall be instituted in the Republic of South Africa. We and you hereby consent to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the South Gauteng High Court, Johannesburg, for any proceedings arising out of or in connection with this agreement.

Each provision of this privacy policy shall apply to the maximum extent permitted by any law, including the Consumer Protection Act No. 68 of 2008 (as may be amended from time to time).

## Online advertising

ZAlebs engages third parties that help it deliver its banner advertisements and other online communications. The third parties may collect and use information about ZAlebs customers to help us understand the offers, promotions, and types of advertising that are most appealing to its customers. The personal information they collect is aggregated and cannot be linked to a person. If you do not wish your personal information to be used in this way, please notify us.

·         Third party vendors, including Google and DoubleClick, show ZAlebs ads on sites on the internet.

·         Third party vendors, including Google and DoubleClick, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to  ZAlebs website.

·         Users may opt out of Google and DoubleClick's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/) or by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about the provisions of this privacy policy, you may contact us through the email address listed on the Contact Us page on our website.

**Back To Top**
